All right, roof's all fixed.
That thing is not going to be leaking
anytime soon.
Is it okay if I put one of
my signs out front of your house?
These are my girlfriend's signs.
Um, not sure
they'll uh if your sign's
going to mesh
well with the other signs.
Probably not not enough room for it.
I don't want to
upset her. You know what I mean?
No, I hear you. I got a brother who's a [ __ ]
Look, how about this?
I'll put my sign
like 5 10 ft away from yours.
That way
they don't bother each other.
- Sure.
- All right. All right. Go ahead.
Thank you. Thank you.
- How's it going?
- Hey, what's up?
Sh. Well, I've never been in a
neighborhood like this. This is uh real
nice.
So, uh how long have you guys lived
here?
I'm sorry. We're not really in the mood
to talk right now. We're in the middle
of some very important messaging.
Oh, okay. Well, all right. Have a good
night.
These guys suck, dude. Don't worry about
it.
No one wants your opinion, flag.
Uh it's American flag to you. And say,
sir.
Uh not in my America.
Yeah, that's cool. That's fine with me,
dude. I'm doing all right.
You ever see
me at the Super Bowl? Pretty big deal.
- Pretty big deal.
- Jesus Christ.
Hey. Hey
- What?
You're not racist?
Uh, no. I'm not racist. Can't you
[ __ ] read?
- That's got to be pretty tough.
- Excuse me?
No, I'm I'm saying like I I try my best.
But there are some neighborhoods, you
know, you go through.
Let me stop you right there.
Not too bad. I just mean like, wow,
Puerto Ricans really love their
fireworks.
- Okay, that's enough.
- You know, I'm just trying to be honest, you know.
It must be really hard. And
that's probably why there's only one of
you.
Well, actually, I'm not racist either.
Oh, I'm sorry. I I I didn't read your
whole sign. Hold on a second.
What are you leaving?
subtext. It's implied.
I'm not seeing it. Is it on the back?
- Please shut the [ __ ] up.
- Oh, okay.
I'm just trying to make some
friends. My bad.
Oh, that's great. Look what you guys
did. You scared him off.
It was nice
having some diversity around here.
Flag. What would you know about
diversity?
I'm everything. I'm like Justin Timberlake.
I'm gay. I'm black. I'm
Frank Sinatra.
I run the whole gamut.
You guys put that black sign in the back
pretty quick once Ukraine got popular.
Sick of every day. Every day we do this.
Okay. Well, the Ukraine needs our help
more
than black people.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Ukraine is glorious country.
Once defined by its beauty, now
Okay, thank you, Ukraine. Thank you.
That's enough.
Dude, are you from Russia?
Hey, can you guys keep it down? I have a
really big game tomorrow.
Whoa. Are you guys seeing what I'm
seeing? Total bee.
That's Sun Valley girl. She's a sweet angel.
- She is a child.
- Actually, she just turned 18.
See, isn't that gross?
Yeah, it's gross when the bed bug guy
says it.
Are you guys talking about me? Stop.
Volleyball girls all we got, and you
guys are trying to ruin it.
Well, I'm here, but I won't be for long.
This listing sold in 2 days.
I guess you
could say Diane did it again.
Oh, shut up, Diane.
No, you shut the [ __ ] up.
Take it easy, Diane.
I don't know what that was, but
I'm into it.
I'm the only [ __ ] sign on this block
doing [ __ ]
Diane, don't make me come down there and
take away your rights.
[ __ ] you, flag.
I might [ __ ] around and out of state.
What the [ __ ] is that?
Oh my god.
Holy [ __ ]
Goddamn white people in these gay ass
sons.
I'm dying. My legs are all [ __ ] up.
Always distracting me. This your fault.
How is this my fault? You're driving.
Oh my god. I'm devastated.
Sorry, baby girl. I'm still here.
That is not vain. I have seen real pain.
Go on and on about it.
You know, I kind of
want to hear Russia's side right now.
Hey, flag.
Is it bad? Is it bad?
Just tell me the truth. Tell me the
truth. I can take it. Please tell me
what it looks like.
Yeah, there's nothing I can do. You're [ __ ]
Hopefully they recycle you into
something cool like a porn.
Yo yo yo. Look at that sign. That thing
sexy.
- Dang, that sign is kind of thick.
- Look at them eyelashes.
Right. Nice little volleyball. I
wouldn't mind spiking that a few times.
Oh my god. My dad would be furious.